So here's the answer. The first one is always equivalent to
答案如下 第一个选项始终等同 s 字符串
the string s, remember what it means to use the colon when
记住在其左边什么内容也没有的情况下使用冒号的意思是什么
there's nothing on the left side means, start from the beginning, and
意思是从起始位置开始
when there's nothing on the right side, means go all the way
当冒号右边什么内容也没有时
to the end. So if there's nothing on on either side, that's
则说明是一直到末尾位置 因此当冒号左右两边都没有内容时
selecting the entire string. So the second one's a little trickier, but
这说明选择了整个字符串 第二个选项略微复杂一些
this also always has the same value as the string s. And
但是这个选项也始终和 s 字符串的值保持一致
the reason is, we have the original string s, and we're concatenating
原因如下 这是原始 s 字符串
to it the string s index 0, colon negative
在其后面 我们加上另外一个 s 字符串 并对其通过0 冒号 -1+1进行索引
1 plus 1. Well, negative 1 plus 1 has the
-1与1相加值为0
value 0. When we index from 0 colon 0, that's
当通过0冒号0进行索引时
an empty string. And the reason that's an empty string
我们发现这是一个空字符串 之所以这是一个空字符串
is because we're starting from 0. And we're stopping just
是因为我们是从0开始 也是在0之前结束
before 0, there are no character between 0 and 0
0和0之间没有字符
so that's an empty string. Adding the empty string to
因此这是一个空字符串
itself, leaves the string empty. And the interesting thing about
在 s 字符串的基础上加一个空字符串 结果还是原字符串
this is, this works even when s is an
有趣的是当 s 为一个空字符串时 这仍然是说得通的
empty string. If s was an empty string, s index
如果 s 是空字符串 s 通过0进行索引
0. That would produce an error. It's trying to
就会产生错误
select the first character from s, and there is no
这是试图从 s 中选择第一个字符
first character since s was an empty string. But
然而 s 中并没有第一个字符 它是一个空字符串
s index 12 colon 12, even though there is no
但是 s 通过12 冒号 12 进行索引
12th character of, of s, since there is no
即使 s 字符串中没有第12个字符
characters between there, it's okay that s doesn't have them.
因为在这个索引区间没有字符 那也没有关系
That's going to valuate to the empty string. So, the third
我们来对空字符串进行评估
one is also always equivalent to s. It's selecting from the
第三个选项也始终等于 s
beginning of the string, position 0, all the way to
它是从字符串的开始进行选择 从0开始
the end. Again, as we saw here, even if s has
一直到结束 再一次 正如我们此处所见
no characters, this is still okay. It will give us
即使 s 字符串没有字符 这也没有关系
the empty string, if s has any characters, it will give
我们会得到一个空字符串 如果 s 中有任何字符
us all the characters in s. This first one is not
我们会得到 s 字符串中的所有字符
equivalent, and this might be a little surprising. It sounds like,
这是第一个不等同于 s 字符串的选项 这个选项可能会有点奇怪
well, it's selecting all the characters from the beginning
它就像是 选择从一开始到最后的所有字符
to the end, because negative 1 is the index of
因为负1是 s 中最后一个字符的索引
the last character in s. But remember that the selection
但是需要注意的一点是这个选项选择的范围不包括最后一个字符
stops before the last character. So what this do, will
而实际 s 字符串的选择范围是每个字符
do will give us every character besides the last one.
包括最后一个字符
So let's see that in the Python interpreter. Were going
我们在 Python 解释器中运行一下
to print s index, colon, negative one, and this will
我们输出 s 字符串 对冒号 负1进行索引之后的内容
give us all the characters except for the last one.
运行之后 我们会得到除了最后一个字符之外的所有字符
So the final one is the most surprising. That this actually
最后一个选项是最出乎意料的
is always equivalent to s. It's equivalent even if s has fewer
这个选项始终等于 s  即使 s 包含的字符不足3个
than 3 characters. So the first part of selecting all the
该选项也始终等同于 s 因为选项的第一部分是
characters from the beginning up to
选择从开头到第三个的字符
position three, not including position three,
不包括第三个字符
and then we're concatenating that with all the characters of s
随后我们在后面加上 s 从第三个到最后的所有字符
from position 3 to the end. If s has less than 3
如果 s 包含的字符少于3个
characters, well this is going to be empty. There are no characters
那这一部分就将成为空字符串
from position 3 to the end. But that's okay, we're going to
从第3个字符到最后没有字符 但是没有关系
add the empty string to the characters before
我们会将空字符串加到第3个之前的字符中
position 3. So here's how that works in
我们来看一下它在 python 解释器中是如何运行的
the python interpreter. We'll do s from position
我们将运行 s 字符串 从起始字符到第3个索引字符
beginning to index 3 and add that s
并将这个 s 字符串加到从第3个索引字符开始到最后一个的字符串 s 上
to index 3 to the end. That produces the same string. And if we do this with a
最终运行得出的是一样的字符串 如果我们运行一个短一点的字符串
shorter string. Let's initialize t to be the string, Hi. We can print from
我们将 t 初始化为字符串 Hi 我们输出 t 字符串从起始字符到第3个位置的字符
t to position 3 plus from t to position 3 to the end. We don't get an error.
加上 t 字符串从第3个字符到最后一个位置的字符 运行之后 我们没有收到错误提示
We get the string Hi out. So, this indexing
我们得到了 Hi 字符串
subsequences is very resilient. It works even when we index
因此 这种索引子序列的方法适应性很好
positions that don't exist in the string. This is
即使我们索引的字符在字符串中并不存在 它仍可以运行
different from when we were doing indexing of particular positions
这种方法区别于从特定位置进行检索
by themselves. If we did index t, index 3,
如果我们检索 t 字符串的第3个字符
that will give us an error. Because there's no character
运行之后显示错误
at position 3.
因为在第3个位置没有字符